<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BricksBreakerApplication</string>
    <string name="my_multiline_textview">
        <font color="GREEN" size="30">About Bricks Breaker</font>\n\n
        <font size="20">Brick Breaker is Block-breaking game in which the player must smash
        a wall of bricks by deflecting a bouncing ball with a paddle.
        The paddle may move horizontally and is controlled with the BlackBerry\'s
        trackwheel, the computer\'s mouse or the touch of a finger (in the
        case of touchscreen). When all the bricks have been destroyed,
        the player advances to a new level. There are 34 levels. There are many
        versions of brick breaker, some in which you can shoot flaming fireballs
        or play with more than one ball if the player gets a power up.\n\n
            The premise of Brick Breaker, like the million other Breakout copy-cats
            for those who have been living in a cave for the last 35-plus years, is
            that bricks are arranged in a pattern at the top of the screen. The player
            controls a paddle that can move left and right. Players start with three lives.\n\n
            The game begins when the player launches a ball towards the bricks. Each time
            the ball hits a brick it breaks the brick and deflects away. If the ball
            deflects back towards the paddle, the player must maneuver the paddle so
            that the ball will deflect back towards the bricks. If the player lets the
            ball fall past the paddle, a life is lost.\n\n
            Bricks can take one or more hits to break, depending on the type of brick,
            as indicated by its color. Silver bricks are obstacles, and the ball cannot
            break them. Each direct hit to a brick is worth 10 points. The ball speeds
            up periodically as the game proceeds, however after a certain speed, the
            ball returns to its original slow speed. If the paddle and the ball strike
            each other a certain number of times, all bricks on the board shift down,
            although once the board shifts a certain distance down, it ceases to shift
            down further.Occasionally, when a ball breaks a brick, a bonus pill will
            fall down vertically. If the player catches a pill, they receive 50 points
            and some game-play change.
        </font></string>

</resources>
